export const quizzes = [
    {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "id" : 1049948,
            "title": "Vikings: Battle of Heirs",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who is the main character in 'Vikings: Battle of Heirs'?",
                "choices": ["A) Amber Doig-Thorne", "B) Gaston Alexander", "C) Iris Papas", "D) Nazeku"],
                "correct_answer": "B) Gaston Alexander"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the central plot point in the movie?",
                "choices": ["A) A Viking treasure hunt", "B) A young Viking discovering his true identity", "C) A love triangle between heirs", "D) A battle for Viking supremacy"],
                "correct_answer": "B) A young Viking discovering his true identity"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which character may have been switched at birth with the King's son?",
                "choices": ["A) Amber Doig-Thorne", "B) Iris Papas", "C) Christabel Clark", "D) Nazeku"],
                "correct_answer": "A) Amber Doig-Thorne"
              },
              {
                "question": "What do others try to do to the young Viking in the movie?",
                "choices": ["A) Offer him a place in their clan", "B) Help him reclaim his rightful place", "C) Take his rightful place as the King's son", "D) Teach him battle skills"],
                "correct_answer": "C) Take his rightful place as the King's son"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor/actress is not part of the main cast?",
                "choices": ["A) Christabel Clark", "B) Iris Papas", "C) Gaston Alexander", "D) Amber Doig-Thorne"],
                "correct_answer": "A) Christabel Clark"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [
              {
                  "title": "Poor Things Movie Quiz",
                  "questions": [
                      {
                          "question": "Who plays the young woman brought back to life in 'Poor Things'?",
                          "choices": ["Emma Stone", "Mark Ruffalo", "Willem Dafoe", "Ramy Youssef"],
                          "correct_answer": "Emma Stone"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which character runs off with a debauched lawyer in 'Poor Things'?",
                          "choices": ["Mark Ruffalo", "Willem Dafoe", "Ramy Youssef", "Christopher Abbott"],
                          "correct_answer": "Emma Stone"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What kind of adventure do the characters embark on in 'Poor Things'?",
                          "choices": ["Space exploration", "Whirlwind adventure across continents", "Underwater expedition", "Jungle trek"],
                          "correct_answer": "Whirlwind adventure across continents"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What purpose does the young woman grow steadfast in pursuing in 'Poor Things'?",
                          "choices": ["Wealth accumulation", "Revenge on society", "Standing for equality and liberation", "Power domination"],
                          "correct_answer": "Standing for equality and liberation"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which actor plays the role of the unorthodox scientist in 'Poor Things'?",
                          "choices": ["Mark Ruffalo", "Willem Dafoe", "Ramy Youssef", "Christopher Abbott"],
                          "correct_answer": "Willem Dafoe"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Migration Movie Trivia",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who plays a role in the duck family in the movie?",
                "choices": ["Kumail Nanjiani", "Elizabeth Banks", "Caspar Jennings", "Awkwafina"],
                "correct_answer": "Caspar Jennings"
              },
              {
                "question": "Where does the Mallard family go on a road trip?",
                "choices": ["Paris", "New York City", "Tokyo", "London"],
                "correct_answer": "New York City"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which family shares thrilling tales of far-flung places with the Mallard family?",
                "choices": ["Goose family", "Swan family", "Duck family", "Penguin family"],
                "correct_answer": "Duck family"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which of the following actors is not part of the cast?",
                "choices": ["Tresi Gazal", "Elizabeth Banks", "Hugh Jackman", "Awkwafina"],
                "correct_answer": "Hugh Jackman"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the first destination of the Mallard family's road trip?",
                "choices": ["New England", "Los Angeles", "Miami", "Chicago"],
                "correct_answer": "New England"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Anyone But You Movie Trivia",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Where do Bea and Ben pretend to be a couple?",
                "choices": ["Paris", "New York", "Australia", "London"],
                "correct_answer": "Australia"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the initial relationship status of Bea and Ben after their first date?",
                "choices": ["Friends", "Enemies", "Strangers", "Lovers"],
                "correct_answer": "Enemies"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor plays the role of Ben in the movie?",
                "choices": ["Sydney Sweeney", "Glen Powell", "Mia Artemis", "Nat Buchanan"],
                "correct_answer": "Glen Powell"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which location serves as the setting for the destination wedding?",
                "choices": ["Italy", "Hawaii", "Australia", "Greece"],
                "correct_answer": "Australia"
              },
              {
                "question": "What do Bea and Ben do when they unexpectedly reunite at the wedding?",
                "choices": ["Ignore each other", "Act like strangers", "Pretend to be siblings", "Pretend to be a couple"],
                "correct_answer": "Pretend to be a couple"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [
              {
                  "title": "Oppenheimer Movie Trivia",
                  "questions": [
                      {
                          "question": "Who played the role of J. Robert Oppenheimer in the movie?",
                          "choices": ["Cillian Murphy", "Matt Damon", "Robert Downey Jr.", "Florence Pugh"],
                          "correct_answer": "Cillian Murphy"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "In which historical event does the movie 'Oppenheimer' primarily focus on?",
                          "choices": ["World War I", "Vietnam War", "World War II", "Cold War"],
                          "correct_answer": "World War II"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which actress is part of the cast of 'Oppenheimer'?",
                          "choices": ["Florence Pugh", "Emily Blunt", "Cillian Murphy", "Matt Damon"],
                          "correct_answer": "Emily Blunt"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What was J. Robert Oppenheimer's significant contribution during World War II?",
                          "choices": ["Tank development", "Atomic bomb development", "Codebreaking", "Aircraft engineering"],
                          "correct_answer": "Atomic bomb development"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which actor does not star in 'Oppenheimer'?",
                          "choices": ["Matt Damon", "Robert Downey Jr.", "Florence Pugh", "Brad Pitt"],
                          "correct_answer": "Brad Pitt"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [
              {
                  "title": "The Weapon Movie Trivia",
                  "questions": [
                      {
                          "question": "Who is the main character in the movie 'The Weapon'?",
                          "choices": ["Tony Schiena", "AnnaLynne McCord", "Sean Patrick Flanery", "Jack Kesy"],
                          "correct_answer": "Tony Schiena"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What is the plot of 'The Weapon' centered around?",
                          "choices": [
                              "Dallas seeking revenge on a mob boss",
                              "A love story between Dallas and a biker gang member",
                              "Dallas' quest for wealth in the Vegas underworld",
                              "A friendship between Dallas and a meth lab owner"
                          ],
                          "correct_answer": "Dallas seeking revenge on a mob boss"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Why does Dallas go on a killing spree in 'The Weapon'?",
                          "choices": [
                              "To rescue his girlfriend from the Vegas mob boss",
                              "To eliminate all biker gangs in the city",
                              "For the thrill of the hunt",
                              "To impress a mysterious employer"
                          ],
                          "correct_answer": "To rescue his girlfriend from the Vegas mob boss"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What makes Dallas a formidable foe in 'The Weapon'?",
                          "choices": [
                              "His exceptional hacking skills",
                              "His negotiation tactics",
                              "His ability to blend in with any crowd",
                              "His lethal combat skills"
                          ],
                          "correct_answer": "His lethal combat skills"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "How does the Vegas mob boss react to Dallas' actions in the movie?",
                          "choices": [
                              "He offers a truce with Dallas",
                              "He releases Dallas' girlfriend unharmed",
                              "He becomes determined to stop Dallas at all costs",
                              "He joins forces with Dallas"
                          ],
                          "correct_answer": "He becomes determined to stop Dallas at all costs"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Meteor Movie Trivia",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who are the two main characters in the movie Meteor?",
                "choices": ["A. Father and daughter", "B. Rancher and young girl", "C. Mercenaries duo", "D. Scientists team"],
                "correct_answer": "B. Rancher and young girl"
              },
              {
                "question": "What triggers the events in the movie Meteor?",
                "choices": ["A. Tsunami", "B. Meteor collision", "C. Volcanic eruption", "D. Alien invasion"],
                "correct_answer": "B. Meteor collision"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor plays the role of the lonely rancher in Meteor?",
                "choices": ["A. Olivia Nash", "B. Thom Hallum", "C. Robert Keith", "D. Jordan Walker Ross"],
                "correct_answer": "C. Robert Keith"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who are the antagonists pursuing the rancher and the young girl?",
                "choices": ["A. Alien creatures", "B. Government agents", "C. Mercenaries", "D. Local law enforcement"],
                "correct_answer": "C. Mercenaries"
              },
              {
                "question": "Where do the events of the movie Meteor primarily take place?",
                "choices": ["A. Mountain town", "B. Desert wilderness", "C. Coastal city", "D. Suburban neighborhood"],
                "correct_answer": "B. Desert wilderness"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Ruthless Movie Trivia",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who plays the role of the high school coach seeking revenge in the movie 'Ruthless'?",
                "choices": ["Dermot Mulroney", "Jeff Fahey", "Melissa Diaz", "Mauricio Mendoza"],
                "correct_answer": "Dermot Mulroney"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the main motivation for the high school coach's actions in 'Ruthless'?",
                "choices": ["To find his missing wallet", "To avenge his daughter's murder", "To win a baseball championship", "To become a famous actor"],
                "correct_answer": "To avenge his daughter's murder"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which character is involved in kidnapping students for a sex trafficking operation in 'Ruthless'?",
                "choices": ["The school principal", "The janitor", "The math teacher", "The cafeteria lady"],
                "correct_answer": "The school principal"
              },
              {
                "question": "What genre does the movie 'Ruthless' belong to?",
                "choices": ["Romantic Comedy", "Sci-Fi Fantasy", "Action Thriller", "Musical"],
                "correct_answer": "Action Thriller"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor is NOT part of the cast of 'Ruthless'?",
                "choices": ["Niko Foster", "Robert De Niro", "Jeff Fahey", "Melissa Diaz"],
                "correct_answer": "Robert De Niro"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Death Alley",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "When does the movie Death Alley take place?",
                "choices": ["1895", "1892", "1900", "1910"],
                "correct_answer": "1892"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who leads the Dalton Gang in the movie Death Alley?",
                "choices": ["Delno Ebie", "Nicholas Barton", "Corey Cannon", "Julia Grace Anderson"],
                "correct_answer": "Delno Ebie"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the aspiration of the Dalton Gang in Death Alley?",
                "choices": ["Become lawmen", "Become famous outlaws", "Settle down peacefully", "Start a business"],
                "correct_answer": "Become famous outlaws"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor plays a role in Death Alley?",
                "choices": ["Jennifer Lopez", "Ryan T. Johnson", "Tom Hanks", "Emma Stone"],
                "correct_answer": "Ryan T. Johnson"
              },
              {
                "question": "What does the Dalton Gang's dream turn into according to Death Alley's plot?",
                "choices": ["A success story", "A fairy tale", "A nightmare", "A comedy"],
                "correct_answer": "A nightmare"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Dune Movie Trivia",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who plays the character Paul Atreides in the movie Dune?",
                "choices": ["Timothée Chalamet", "Oscar Isaac", "Josh Brolin", "Stellan Skarsgård"],
                "correct_answer": "Timothée Chalamet"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the dangerous planet that Paul Atreides must travel to in Dune?",
                "choices": ["Arrakis", "Tatooine", "Endor", "Hoth"],
                "correct_answer": "Arrakis"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which precious resource is at the center of the conflict in the movie Dune?",
                "choices": ["Melange", "Gold", "Diamonds", "Oil"],
                "correct_answer": "Melange"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who portrays Lady Jessica, Paul's mother, in Dune?",
                "choices": ["Rebecca Ferguson", "Timothée Chalamet", "Oscar Isaac", "Josh Brolin"],
                "correct_answer": "Rebecca Ferguson"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor plays the character Gurney Halleck in Dune?",
                "choices": ["Josh Brolin", "Stellan Skarsgård", "Oscar Isaac", "Timothée Chalamet"],
                "correct_answer": "Josh Brolin"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "The Marvels Quiz",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who plays Carol Danvers, aka Captain Marvel, in the movie The Marvels?",
                "choices": ["Brie Larson", "Teyonah Parris", "Iman Vellani", "Zawe Ashton"],
                "correct_answer": "Brie Larson"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which character's powers become entangled with those of Carol Danvers in The Marvels?",
                "choices": ["Kamala Khan", "Monica Rambeau", "Supreme Intelligence", "Nick Fury"],
                "correct_answer": "Kamala Khan"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the name of Carol Danvers' estranged niece who is a S.A.B.E.R. astronaut in The Marvels?",
                "choices": ["Monica Rambeau", "Kamala Khan", "Maria Rambeau", "Annette Bening"],
                "correct_answer": "Monica Rambeau"
              },
              {
                "question": "Where does Carol Danvers' duty send her to in The Marvels?",
                "choices": ["Anomalous wormhole", "Kree homeworld", "Earth's moon", "Asgard"],
                "correct_answer": "Anomalous wormhole"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who is the main antagonist in The Marvels?",
                "choices": ["Supreme Intelligence", "Thanos", "Loki", "Red Skull"],
                "correct_answer": "Supreme Intelligence"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "The OctoGames Trivia",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "What do the contestants compete for in The OctoGames?",
                "choices": ["Money prize", "Fame and a YouTube channel", "Travel vouchers", "New cars"],
                "correct_answer": "Fame and a YouTube channel"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who is the mysterious content creator in The OctoGames?",
                "choices": ["JaxPro", "MaxGamer", "AceVids", "MysteryMan"],
                "correct_answer": "JaxPro"
              },
              {
                "question": "How many contestants participate in The OctoGames?",
                "choices": ["Four", "Six", "Eight", "Ten"],
                "correct_answer": "Eight"
              },
              {
                "question": "What type of games do the contestants compete in?",
                "choices": ["Video games", "Children's games", "Board games", "Puzzle games"],
                "correct_answer": "Children's games"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which character is played by Lacy Hartselle in The OctoGames?",
                "choices": ["Jack", "Emily", "Sophia", "Lindsay"],
                "correct_answer": "Lindsay"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who seeks revenge on Aquaman for his father's death in the movie?",
                "choices": ["Aquaman", "Black Manta", "Atlantis Council", "Prison Guards"],
                "correct_answer": "Black Manta"
              },
              {
                "question": "What power does Black Manta wield in the movie?",
                "choices": ["Black Trident", "Golden Sword", "Silver Shield", "Platinum Dagger"],
                "correct_answer": "Black Trident"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who does Aquaman forge an alliance with to defend Atlantis?",
                "choices": ["His childhood friend", "His neighbor", "His imprisoned brother", "A stranger"],
                "correct_answer": "His imprisoned brother"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor plays the role of Aquaman in the movie?",
                "choices": ["Patrick Wilson", "Yahya Abdul-Mateen II", "Randall Park", "Jason Momoa"],
                "correct_answer": "Jason Momoa"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who must Aquaman and his brother protect the kingdom from?",
                "choices": ["Friendly Mermaids", "Black Manta", "Sea Turtles", "Atlantis Enemies"],
                "correct_answer": "Black Manta"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [
              {
                  "title": "The Kindred Movie Trivia",
                  "questions": [
                      {
                          "question": "Who plays the role of the young mother investigating her father's death in 'The Kindred'?",
                          "choices": ["April Pearson", "Blake Harrison", "James Cosmo", "Samantha Bond"],
                          "correct_answer": "April Pearson"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What is the main focus of the investigation by the young mother in 'The Kindred'?",
                          "choices": ["Her father's disappearance", "A family curse", "An unsolved mystery from 30 years ago", "A hidden treasure"],
                          "correct_answer": "An unsolved mystery from 30 years ago"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which character in 'The Kindred' is haunted by spirits?",
                          "choices": ["April Pearson", "Blake Harrison", "James Cosmo", "Samantha Bond"],
                          "correct_answer": "April Pearson"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "In 'The Kindred,' what dark family history is discovered by the young mother that could endanger her child?",
                          "choices": ["A history of royalty", "A history of witchcraft", "A history of medical experiments", "A history of violence"],
                          "correct_answer": "A history of violence"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which actor from the cast of 'The Kindred' is known for the role of Mark Donovan in 'The Inbetweeners'?",
                          "choices": ["April Pearson", "Blake Harrison", "James Cosmo", "Steve Oram"],
                          "correct_answer": "Blake Harrison"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Wish Movie Quiz",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in the movie 'Wish'?",
                "choices": ["Emma", "Asha", "Sophia", "Luna"],
                "correct_answer": "Asha"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who answers Asha's powerful wish in 'Wish'?",
                "choices": ["Moon", "Star", "Sun", "Comet"],
                "correct_answer": "Star"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the name of the formidable foe Asha and Star confront in 'Wish'?",
                "choices": ["Queen Seraphina", "King Magnifico", "Emperor Orion", "Princess Celestia"],
                "correct_answer": "King Magnifico"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor plays the role of Asha in the movie 'Wish'?",
                "choices": ["Ariana DeBose", "Chris Pine", "Alan Tudyk", "Angelique Cabral"],
                "correct_answer": "Ariana DeBose"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who portrays the character of King Magnifico in 'Wish'?",
                "choices": ["Chris Pine", "Alan Tudyk", "Victor Garber", "Angelique Cabral"],
                "correct_answer": "Victor Garber"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Agent Game Movie Trivia",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who is the lead character in Agent Game?",
                "choices": ["Harris", "Olsen", "Visser", "Gibson"],
                "correct_answer": "Harris"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is Harris' role at the CIA?",
                "choices": ["Interrogator", "Field Agent", "Analyst", "Technician"],
                "correct_answer": "Interrogator"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who is the senior intelligence officer in the movie?",
                "choices": ["Olsen", "Visser", "Mulroney", "Canto"],
                "correct_answer": "Olsen"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor plays the character of Harris?",
                "choices": ["Mel Gibson", "Dermot Mulroney", "Adan Canto", "Jason Isaacs"],
                "correct_answer": "Mel Gibson"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the main objective of Harris and his allies in the movie?",
                "choices": ["Uncover the truth", "Start a war", "Escape the country", "Join the enemy"],
                "correct_answer": "Uncover the truth"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [{
                  "title": "The Five Movie Quiz",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "Who enlists the help of five strangers to execute a bank robbery in the movie 'The Five'?",
                          "choices": ["John Marrs", "Todd South", "A scorned woman", "Tom Dragt"],
                          "correct_answer": "A scorned woman"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What is the main plot of 'The Five' movie?",
                          "choices": ["Planning a wedding", "Robbing a bank", "Becoming detectives", "Starting a business"],
                          "correct_answer": "Robbing a bank"
                      }
                  ]
              },
              {
                  "title": "The Five Movie Quiz",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "Which character anxiously awaits the scorned woman's arrival with the stolen money?",
                          "choices": ["Todd South", "Tom Dragt", "Michael P. Walker", "Cat Roberts"],
                          "correct_answer": "Todd South"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What do the crew members wonder about in 'The Five' movie?",
                          "choices": ["If they have been betrayed", "If the weather is nice", "What to eat for dinner", "Where to go on vacation"],
                          "correct_answer": "If they have been betrayed"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [
              {
                  "title": "Dora: Say Hola to Adventure!",
                  "questions": [
                      {
                          "question": "Who is the world's most famous exploradora in the movie?",
                          "choices": ["Dora", "Diego", "Boots", "Swiper"],
                          "correct_answer": "Dora"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Where do Dora and her friends embark on new adventures?",
                          "choices": ["Desert", "Rainforest", "Ocean", "City"],
                          "correct_answer": "Rainforest"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which character is voiced by Diana Zermeño?",
                          "choices": ["Boots", "Swiper", "Map", "Backpack"],
                          "correct_answer": "Map"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What is the name of the character voiced by Marc Weiner?",
                          "choices": ["Boots", "Diego", "Tico", "Fiesta Trio"],
                          "correct_answer": "Fiesta Trio"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Who is not a part of Dora's main group of friends?",
                          "choices": ["Swiper", "Backpack", "Isa", "Tico"],
                          "correct_answer": "Swiper"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Fast X",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who plays the role of Dom Toretto in the movie Fast X?",
                "choices": ["Vin Diesel", "John Cena", "Tyrese Gibson", "Ludacris"],
                "correct_answer": "Vin Diesel"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the main threat the family faces in Fast X?",
                "choices": ["Nuclear attack", "Alien invasion", "Blood revenge", "Financial collapse"],
                "correct_answer": "Blood revenge"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which character is determined to destroy everything and everyone Dom loves?",
                "choices": ["Letty", "Roman", "Owen Shaw", "Cipher"],
                "correct_answer": "Cipher"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is the primary driving force for the main antagonist in Fast X?",
                "choices": ["Money", "Power", "Blood revenge", "Fame"],
                "correct_answer": "Blood revenge"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who among the following is NOT part of Dom's family in Fast X?",
                "choices": ["Tyrese Gibson", "John Cena", "Ludacris", "Gal Gadot"],
                "correct_answer": "Gal Gadot"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [{
                  "title": "The Family Plan Trivia",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "What is Dan Morgan's profession before becoming a car salesman?",
                          "choices": ["A. Lawyer", "B. Doctor", "C. Assassin", "D. Teacher"],
                          "correct_answer": "C. Assassin"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Why does Dan have to take his family on a road trip?",
                          "choices": ["A. Vacation request from his wife", "B. Witness protection program", "C. Family bonding experience", "D. Business trip"],
                          "correct_answer": "B. Witness protection program"
                      }
                  ]
              },
              {
                  "title": "The Family Plan Trivia",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "Who plays the role of Dan Morgan in the movie?",
                          "choices": ["A. Mark Wahlberg", "B. Maggie Q", "C. Michelle Monaghan", "D. Zoe Colletti"],
                          "correct_answer": "A. Mark Wahlberg"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What is the main challenge Dan faces on the road trip?",
                          "choices": ["A. Car breakdown", "B. Unplanned detour", "C. Bad weather", "D. Pursuers from his past"],
                          "correct_answer": "D. Pursuers from his past"
                      }
                  ]
              },
              {
                  "title": "The Family Plan Trivia",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "Which character in the movie is unaware of Dan's past as an assassin?",
                          "choices": ["A. Wife", "B. Son", "C. Daughter", "D. Best friend"],
                          "correct_answer": "C. Daughter"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What genre does 'The Family Plan' fall under?",
                          "choices": ["A. Comedy", "B. Action", "C. Romance", "D. Horror"],
                          "correct_answer": "B. Action"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [{
                  "title": "The Hunger Games: The Ballad of Songbirds & Snakes",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "Who is the main character in 'The Hunger Games: The Ballad of Songbirds & Snakes'?",
                          "choices": ["Lucy Gray Baird", "Coriolanus Snow", "Katniss Everdeen", "Peeta Mellark"],
                          "correct_answer": "Coriolanus Snow"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which district is Lucy Gray Baird from?",
                          "choices": ["District 1", "District 5", "District 12", "District 8"],
                          "correct_answer": "District 12"
                      }
                  ]
              },
              {
                  "title": "The Hunger Games: The Ballad of Songbirds & Snakes",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "Who portrays Coriolanus Snow in the movie?",
                          "choices": ["Tom Blyth", "Rachel Zegler", "Peter Dinklage", "Jason Schwartzman"],
                          "correct_answer": "Tom Blyth"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which character does Hunter Schafer play?",
                          "choices": ["Lucy Gray Baird", "Katniss Everdeen", "Effie Trinket", "Gale Hawthorne"],
                          "correct_answer": "Lucy Gray Baird"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [{
                  "title": "Napoleon",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "Who is set to portray Napoleon Bonaparte in the movie?",
                          "choices": ["Joaquin Phoenix", "Vanessa Kirby", "Tahar Rahim", "Rupert Everett"],
                          "correct_answer": "Joaquin Phoenix"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which aspect of Napoleon's life is explored through the movie's plot?",
                          "choices": ["His rise and fall as French Emperor", "His art skills", "His cooking abilities", "His gardening hobby"],
                          "correct_answer": "His rise and fall as French Emperor"
                      }
                  ]
              },
              {
                  "title": "Napoleon",
                  "questions": [{
                          "question": "Who plays the role of Napoleon's wife, Josephine?",
                          "choices": ["Vanessa Kirby", "Mark Bonnar", "Rupert Everett", "Tahar Rahim"],
                          "correct_answer": "Vanessa Kirby"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "What kind of relationship does Napoleon have with Josephine in the movie?",
                          "choices": ["Addictive and volatile", "Stable and serene", "Distant and cold", "Friendly and supportive"],
                          "correct_answer": "Addictive and volatile"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "The Super Mario Bros. Movie",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who plays the character Mario in 'The Super Mario Bros. Movie'?",
                "choices": ["Chris Pratt", "Charlie Day", "Jack Black", "Keegan-Michael Key"],
                "correct_answer": "Chris Pratt"
              },
              {
                "question": "What profession do the brothers Mario and Luigi have at the beginning of the movie?",
                "choices": ["Taxi Drivers", "Plumbers", "Electricians", "Carpenters"],
                "correct_answer": "Plumbers"
              },
              {
                "question": "What magical world do Mario and Luigi wander into?",
                "choices": ["Mushroom Kingdom", "Candy Land", "Neverland", "Oz"],
                "correct_answer": "Mushroom Kingdom"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who is Mario searching for when he embarks on an epic quest in the movie?",
                "choices": ["Princess Peach", "Luigi", "Bowser", "Toad"],
                "correct_answer": "Luigi"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor plays Luigi in 'The Super Mario Bros. Movie'?",
                "choices": ["Anya Taylor-Joy", "Jack Black", "Chris Pratt", "Keegan-Michael Key"],
                "correct_answer": "Anya Taylor-Joy"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Spider-Man: Across the Spider-Verse",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who does Miles reunite with in 'Across the Spider-Verse'?",
                "choices": ["Gwen Stacy", "Mary Jane Watson", "Felicia Hardy", "Betty Brant"],
                "correct_answer": "Gwen Stacy"
              },
              {
                "question": "What society does Miles encounter in the Multiverse?",
                "choices": ["Spider Society", "Hulk Society", "Wolverine Society", "Avengers Society"],
                "correct_answer": "Spider Society"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor voices the character of Miles Morales?",
                "choices": ["Shameik Moore", "Hailee Steinfeld", "Jason Schwartzman", "Oscar Isaac"],
                "correct_answer": "Shameik Moore"
              },
              {
                "question": "Who must Miles set out to save on his own?",
                "choices": ["Those he loves most", "Strangers", "Enemies", "Superheroes"],
                "correct_answer": "Those he loves most"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which character clashes with Miles over handling a new threat?",
                "choices": ["Spider Society", "Gwen Stacy", "Peter Parker", "Venom"],
                "correct_answer": "Spider Society"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "quizzes": [
          {
            "title": "Transformers: Rise of the Beasts",
            "questions": [
              {
                "question": "Who must team up with Optimus Prime and the Autobots to combat the new threat in the movie?",
                "choices": ["A) Decepticons", "B) Maximals", "C) Predacons", "D) Constructicons"],
                "correct_answer": "B) Maximals"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actors are part of the cast for 'Transformers: Rise of the Beasts'?",
                "choices": ["A) Tom Hanks", "B) Anthony Ramos", "C) Scarlett Johansson", "D) Emma Stone"],
                "correct_answer": "B) Anthony Ramos"
              },
              {
                "question": "What is Noah and Elena's primary goal in the movie?",
                "choices": ["A) Capture the Autobots", "B) Protect the new threat", "C) Help the Transformers save Earth", "D) Side with the Decepticons"],
                "correct_answer": "C) Help the Transformers save Earth"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which faction do Optimus Prime and the Autobots join forces with in 'Transformers: Rise of the Beasts'?",
                "choices": ["A) Maximals", "B) Dinobots", "C) Insecticons", "D) Aerialbots"],
                "correct_answer": "A) Maximals"
              },
              {
                "question": "Which actor provides the voice for Optimus Prime in the movie?",
                "choices": ["A) Ron Perlman", "B) Peter Dinklage", "C) Anthony Ramos", "D) Peter Cullen"],
                "correct_answer": "D) Peter Cullen"
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
          "quizzes": [
              {
                  "title": "Avatar: The Way of Water",
                  "questions": [
                      {
                          "question": "Who are the main characters in Avatar: The Way of Water?",
                          "choices": ["Jake and Neytiri", "Jack and Rose", "John and Mary", "Peter and Susan"],
                          "correct_answer": "Jake and Neytiri"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "When is Avatar: The Way of Water set in relation to the first film?",
                          "choices": ["Hundreds of years before", "More than a decade after", "Simultaneously", "A few months after"],
                          "correct_answer": "More than a decade after"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which actress portrays Neytiri in the movie?",
                          "choices": ["Zoe Saldaña", "Scarlett Johansson", "Jennifer Lawrence", "Emma Stone"],
                          "correct_answer": "Zoe Saldaña"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Who plays the character of Jake in Avatar: The Way of Water?",
                          "choices": ["Sam Smith", "Sam Worthington", "Sam Rockwell", "Sam Mendes"],
                          "correct_answer": "Sam Worthington"
                      },
                      {
                          "question": "Which actor from the first film reprises his role in Avatar: The Way of Water?",
                          "choices": ["Tom Cruise", "Stephen Lang", "Robert Downey Jr.", "Brad Pitt"],
                          "correct_answer": "Stephen Lang"
                      }
                  ]
              }
          ]
      }

]